MERCY NARJINARY

ABOUT ME

Personable and dedicated Customer Service Representative with Extensive experience in Customer Support Industry. Solid team player with upbeat, positive attitude and proven skills in establishing rapport With clients. Motivated to maintain customer satisfaction and Contribute to company success. Specialising in quality, speed and Process optimisation. Articulate, enthusiastic and results-orientated With demonstrated passion for building relationships, cultivating and growing businesses.

Phone

+91-9599583247

Email

mercyjohn876@gmail.com

Address

H.no-162, Sec-12 Railway enclave, Pratap vihar Ghaziabad.

Website

www.naukri.com

EDUCATION

HR. Institute of science & technology (CCS. University)

Bachelor of Business Administration (2018-2021)

Holy trinity church school (ICSE & ISC)

Completed my 10th & 12th-Science (2015-2018)

EXPERTISE

- Telemarketing
- Online Customer Care
- Customer complaint resolution
- Telesales
- · Customer correspondence processing
- Good sales ability

EXPERIENCE

KW. Group (2021-2022)

Rajnagar Extension, Ghaziabad (U.P)

Sales executive

- Customer-focused and dedicated to delivering high quality service
- Present and discuss our strategic master marketing plan
- Prepare detailed list of property comparable and learn our most effective way to do sale
- Keeping track of your progress daily through our tracking pipeline qualifications
- Extremely strong phone calls
- Enthusistic with excellent people skills
- Passion for sales
- Self-starter with high degree of self-confidence and motivation
- Dedication to professionalism and accountable to results

Tech Mahindra (2022-2023)

Sec-127 Tech Boulevard, Noida (U.P)

Customer Support Associate

- Educate customers on product features or additional services to meet their needs
- Management of all drug and background requirements and entity
- Perform oversight of all internal and external deliverables
- Educating clients with new applications, procedure, systems and initiatives
- The ability to multi-task and stay organized
- Great communication skills and experience working on a team
- · A high attention to detail
- Critical thinking and problem solving skills
- Experience working on PC
- Ability to work quickly under pressure
- A friendly and professional demeanor

DECLARATION

I Hereby declare that all the details mentioned above are in accordance with the truth and fact as per my knowledge and I hold the responsibility for the correctness of the above-mentioned particulars.

NAME: Mercy Narjinary

DATE: SIGNATURE